<forum name="hardforum">
      <post id="0bfca667-1e84-468d-85d8-54a765f9050e" section="Video Cards" discussion="Ashes of the Singularity Day 1 Benchmark Preview @ [H]">"Ashes of the Singularity Day 1 Benchmark Preview - The new Ashes of the Singularity game has finally been released on the PC. This game supports DX11 and the new DX12 API with advanced features. In this Day 1 Benchmark Preview we will run a few cards through the in-game canned benchmark comparing DX11 versus DX12 performance and NVIDIA versus AMD performance."</post>
   <post id="6054109d-8179-418e-8b6d-43fd1586fe95" section="Video Cards" discussion="Rise of the Tomb Raider DX11 vs. DX12 Review @ [H]">"Rise of the Tomb Raider DX11 vs. DX12 Review - Rise of the Tomb Raider has recently received a new patch which adds DX12 API support, in addition the patch adds NVIDIA VXAO Ambient Occlusion technology, however just under DX11. In this evaluation we will find out if DX12 is beneficial to the gameplay experience currently and how it impacts certain GPUs."</post>
   <post id="e0bbaaaa-5cf3-44a8-bfc3-4110e10b13ed" section="Video Cards" discussion="4 Weeks with NVIDIA TITAN X SLI at 4K Resolution @ [H]">"4 Weeks with NVIDIA TITAN X SLI at 4K Resolution - What do you get when you take two NVIDIA GeForce TITAN X video cards, configure those for SLI, and set those at your feet for four or more weeks? We give our thoughts and opinions about actually using these behemoth GPUs in our system for weeks and weeks and focus on gaming performance, sound profile, heat generation, and general usability."</post>
   <post id="b233ff47-7cad-47dd-b269-da5c65e2e969" section="Video Cards" discussion="Far Cry Primal Video Card Performance Review @ [H]">"Far Cry Primal Video Card Performance Review - A new game in the Far Cry series is out on the PC called Far Cry Primal. We will run FCP through its paces on six video cards including SLI and CrossFire with the latest drivers and game patch to see what it takes to push these pixels. We will discuss this games stripped down graphics quality compared to Far Cry 4 and what it means for gaming."</post>
   <post id="7f4d7816-7c9d-4b2b-bd7c-047b5b56912d" section="Video Cards" discussion="Rise of the Tomb Raider Video Card Performance Review @ [H]">"Rise of the Tomb Raider Video Card Performance Review - A new Tomb Raider game is out, Rise of the Tomb Raider. We take RoTR and find out how it performs and compares on no less than 14 of today's latest video card offerings from the AMD and NVIDIA GPU lineups from top-to-bottom using the latest drivers and game patch v1.0 build 610.1_64."</post>
   <post id="51e73fa7-fe50-4c8b-bdb8-7782dfe22879" section="Video Cards" discussion="Fallout 4 Patch 1.3 New Image Quality Features @ [H]">"Fallout 4 Patch 1.3 New Image Quality Features - A new patch, version 1.3.47 is out for Fallout 4 and with it brings a couple of big image quality improvements. HBAO+ Ambient Occlusion is added as well as hardware driven Particle Weapon Debris. We will compare these new image quality features and see how they help improve the gameplay experience of Fallout 4."</post>
   <post id="68bea4ac-2118-473b-bec8-50066879cde5" section="Video Cards" discussion="Rise of the Tomb Raider Graphics Features Performance @ [H]">"Rise of the Tomb Raider Graphics Features Performance - We will take the new game Rise of the Tomb Raider and deep-dive into specific graphics features performance. We will find out how each one affects performance and if AMD or NVIDIA GPUs are better at certain features. We will also evaluate VRAM utilization of features. We are using the latest patch v1.0 build 623.2."</post>
   <post id="fd754e4c-df84-4a77-bdf2-58f01523661d" section="Video Cards" discussion="4k@60 vs 4k@30. Resource usage">"What's the difference in resource usage (cpu, memory, etc) between 60hz and 30hz 4k? I mean if Windows desktop is being laggy at 60hz (while watching 4k video), is it going to be any better at 30hz? I don't have any 4k monitors/tv to test out yet. Just curious about technicalities"</post>
   <post id="0191a72d-933d-47f8-a930-645c1ffff528" section="Video Cards" discussion="Clearing Video Cards">"I had a GTX 770 DCII 2GB that I had in my system that I then replaced with a 390 that I never used. I then got a 980ti for a 1440p 144hz monitor and now I have two cards leftover. Depending on when the '1080' is released there's the possibility that I can trade up via EVGA. There's also the possibility of me not being able to trade up and selling the 980ti. It would be nice to clear out the rack. What would you recommend selling?"</post>
   <post id="d80f0397-3cff-4426-93dd-9a256e67da59" section="Video Cards" discussion="Max Video Card for i7 920">"Hi Folks, I have a PC that I built in late 2009 that's has 12GB RAM, i7 920 @ 3.7 Ghz running on a Asus P6T motherboard. I'm trying to determine what's the highest end video card I should put in to this PC. I'm assuming putting something like a GTX 980 would be overkill and the PC would not take full advantage of the video card. What is the best way to figure out the PCs limitation in terms of GPU?"</post>
   <post id="bb7b85ab-e821-4002-9033-fc5b42e954ca" section="Video Cards" discussion="PC reboots when video card is under stress">"Hello, I have the following problem: a while ago I was doing some work that's GPU intensive, and at the exact second I started it and the video card went 100%, the PC reboots itself. To check that it wasn't a problem specific to the task I was doing, I tried some games like Fallout 4 and GTA V (which a couple of months back I had played with no problems) and I got the same results, while other less consuming games like League of Legends run with no problems (most of the time. Sometimes it reboots too). This happens in both Linux and Windows, so I kind of discarded that it's software related. I also run 3DMark's benchmarks, with mixed results. The first and most basic benchmark, Ice Storm, runs fine, but the second one, Cloud Gate, makes the PC reboot instantly. The Furmark GPU stress test reboots instantly. Because I lack hardware knowledge, I find it difficult to diagnose if the problem is in the video card, or if it's some problem with the power supply. Relevant hardware: Video card: Gigabyte GTX 980 ti. PS: Thermaltake Smart 750w 80plus Bronze Both have 6 months of use."</post>
   <post id="866bd9ca-50c4-4e5f-ba6e-7560b7079e35" section="Video Cards" discussion="Going from a 780 to either a 970 or 390x need advice.">"So I've done some recent upgrades (6700K overclocked to 4.6Ghz , 16GB DDR4 3000mhz) to my well aged i7 930 setup (wow night and day difference!). My GTX 780 is next on the chopping block but I'm conflicted. I haven't really been following much of the past few years of GPU's and based on what I've read from benchmarks to user impressions I can't decide what card should be my next upgrade. I know Nvidia and AMD have new series cards coming sometime this year but I'm not really wanting to wait because I've got my friends all bugging me to start playing again (CS : GO , The Division and so on) so I want something better and competitive right now. I have a G-sync 1080p monitor and a 3 x Qnix setup (so 1440p) so that's the resolutions I'll be dealing with. Have zero interest in 4K and likely won't for sometime. VR isn't important because its in its infancy and right now I feel like I would rather wait for the second or third generation VR headsets before jumping in on that. So upgrading to a Freesync monitor is also really unlikely because I want a 1440p IPS that isn't a luck of the draw in terms of panel lottery (I've read people have returned up to 10 monitors and continued to always have problems so not really wanting to do that). Also I don't plan to run all 3 1440p Qnix's at the same time while gaming just one and the G-sync monitor now and again. I know the 970 has a crippled memory interface but how often does that effect VRAM heavy games? Will it be a serious issue in the future? Also from what I've seen the 390x shows varying performance and right now in Direct X 11 it seems inferior in a lot of benchmarks ( no offense to any fans just what I've been reading ) to the 970 which offers more stable fps while the 390x can climb higher in terms of fps but often has frequent dips. Also I have no idea how AMD drivers are. Last time I used an AMD card drivers were an absolute nightmare. What's everyone's opinion? Also I don't SLI. Its a pain in the ass. I do not feel like dealing with SLI malfunctions with every game or new driver release so single card solution only. Also the 980ti is too expensive for my blood right now so that's out of the question. Budget $400 as well. Thanks!"</post>
</forum>
